# **Ederson Arrieta**

Jr.Software Developer

# **Contact information**

#### Cell:

(+506) 8435 5028

#### Fmail:

earrietam1997@gmail.com

#### Adress:

Ulloa, Heredia Costa Rica.

### **Online CV:**

https://eder126.github.io/Curriculum/

### **Education**

# Cenfotec University

Tecnical degree in Software Engineering

- Design Pattern Programming
   Project: Board game inspired by Snakes and Ladders with turn based combat against PC opponent. Developed with: Java, JavaFx.
- Data Structures
   Project: School registration system, using mainly pointers to gather detailed reports. Developed with: C++.
- Proyecto 2
   Project: Food delivery service/web application trying to compete against Rappi,
   Uber Eats and Glovo. Developed with: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, SQL. APIs: Twilio, SendGrid, IronPDF, GMaps.
- Proyecto 1
   Project: Online library trying to compete against Amazon. Focused on Online shopping, either physical or digital, and online Lecture Clubs. Developed with: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, MongoDB.

# **Experience**

# **MBO Specialist**

### Amazon

Dec. 2016 to May 2018

- Improved internal procedures in regards to user experience using the Vendor Central platform.
- Worked with sensitive high brand information to improve the customers experience when shopping in the Amazon website.
- Functioned as a Point of Contact in regards to the SOP's of said process.

### **Vendor Central Associate**

#### Amazon

Jun. 2016 to Dec. 2016

- Provided assistance in phone and email contacts from Amazon Vendors from the Vendors program.
- Assisted temporarily as a POC to peers in regards to our policies and procedures.
- Assisted temporarily as a Supervisor to take control of escalations and find solutions to said situations.

# **Advantage Associate**

### **Amazon**

Jan. 2016 to Jun. 2016

- Helped establish the standard procedure and metrics to pursue when dealing with Vendors of the Amazon Advantage program.
- Handled alongside the team the first ever phone contacts for Amazon Advantage Vendors in the world.
- Helped restructure broken/imperfect procedures up to a point where they could be considered reliable and standard.

# **Summary**

Worked in Amazon for nearly 3 years in multiple fields, maintaining consistent metrics during my time, succeeding and learning as an integral part of my professional growth.

Once I decided to move forward from this opportunity, I focused on continuing my studies in the field of programming at Cenfotec, as I look forward to developing my own ideas in video games, as a personal goal.

Just recently I received my Technical Degree and I'm looking forward to prove my worth in programming to any company that allows me to show and expand my skills. My main objective at this point in time is to continue to grow and learn from new experiences.

# **Technologies**

- .NET.
- Java, JavaFx.
- HTML/CSS, Node, Express, MongoDB.
- Twilio, SendGrid, IronPDF, GMaps.
- PostMan, Git, AzureDevOps, Visual Paradigm, Visual Studio.

# **Skills**

- Spanish native.
- English 90%.
- · Positive attitude.
- · Problem solver.
- Fast learner and adaptable to new circumstances.
- Willing to step in unknown territory in order to learn.